[
  {
    "question": "to be called",
    "answer": "heißen"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am called",
    "answer": "ich heiße"
  },
  {
    "question": "you are called",
    "answer": "du heißt"
  },
  {
    "question": "he is called",
    "answer": "er heißt"
  },
  {
    "question": "she is called",
    "answer": "sie heißt"
  },
  {
    "question": "it is called",
    "answer": "es heißt"
  },
  {
    "question": "we are called",
    "answer": "wir heißen"
  },
  {
    "question": "you (plural) are called",
    "answer": "ihr heißt"
  },
  {
    "question": "they are called",
    "answer": "sie heißen"
  },
  {
    "question": "you (formal) are called",
    "answer": "Sie heißen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to come",
    "answer": "kommen"
  },
  {
    "question": "I come",
    "answer": "ich komme"
  },
  {
    "question": "you come",
    "answer": "du kommst"
  },
  {
    "question": "he comes",
    "answer": "er kommt"
  },
  {
    "question": "she comes",
    "answer": "sie kommt"
  },
  {
    "question": "it comes",
    "answer": "es kommt"
  },
  {
    "question": "we come",
    "answer": "wir kommen"
  },
  {
    "question": "you (plural) come",
    "answer": "ihr kommt"
  },
  {
    "question": "they come",
    "answer": "sie kommen"
  },
  {
    "question": "you (formal) come",
    "answer": "Sie kommen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to live (reside)",
    "answer": "wohnen"
  },
  {
    "question": "I live",
    "answer": "ich wohne"
  },
  {
    "question": "you live",
    "answer": "du wohnst"
  },
  {
    "question": "he lives",
    "answer": "er wohnt"
  },
  {
    "question": "she lives",
    "answer": "sie wohnt"
  },
  {
    "question": "it lives",
    "answer": "es wohnt"
  },
  {
    "question": "we live",
    "answer": "wir wohnen"
  },
  {
    "question": "you (plural) live",
    "answer": "ihr wohnt"
  },
  {
    "question": "they live",
    "answer": "sie wohnen"
  },
  {
    "question": "you (formal) live",
    "answer": "Sie wohnen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to be",
    "answer": "sein"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am",
    "answer": "ich bin"
  },
  {
    "question": "you are",
    "answer": "du bist"
  },
  {
    "question": "he is",
    "answer": "er ist"
  },
  {
    "question": "she is",
    "answer": "sie ist"
  },
  {
    "question": "it is",
    "answer": "es ist"
  },
  {
    "question": "we are",
    "answer": "wir sind"
  },
  {
    "question": "you (plural) are",
    "answer": "ihr seid"
  },
  {
    "question": "they are",
    "answer": "sie sind"
  },
  {
    "question": "you (formal) are",
    "answer": "Sie sind"
  },
  {
    "question": "to travel",
    "answer": "reisen"
  },
  {
    "question": "I travel",
    "answer": "ich reise"
  },
  {
    "question": "you travel",
    "answer": "du reist"
  },
  {
    "question": "he travels",
    "answer": "er reist"
  },
  {
    "question": "she travels",
    "answer": "sie reist"
  },
  {
    "question": "it travels",
    "answer": "es reist"
  },
  {
    "question": "we travel",
    "answer": "wir reisen"
  },
  {
    "question": "you (plural) travel",
    "answer": "ihr reist"
  },
  {
    "question": "they travel",
    "answer": "sie reisen"
  },
  {
    "question": "you (formal) travel",
    "answer": "Sie reisen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to live (exist)",
    "answer": "leben"
  },
  {
    "question": "I live (exist)",
    "answer": "ich lebe"
  },
  {
    "question": "you live (exist)",
    "answer": "du lebst"
  },
  {
    "question": "he lives (exist)",
    "answer": "er lebt"
  },
  {
    "question": "she lives (exist)",
    "answer": "sie lebt"
  },
  {
    "question": "it lives (exist)",
    "answer": "es lebt"
  },
  {
    "question": "we live (exist)",
    "answer": "wir leben"
  },
  {
    "question": "you (plural) live (exist)",
    "answer": "ihr lebt"
  },
  {
    "question": "they live (exist)",
    "answer": "sie leben"
  },
  {
    "question": "you (formal) live (exist)",
    "answer": "Sie leben"
  },
  {
    "question": "person",
    "answer": "die Person"
  },
  {
    "question": "family",
    "answer": "die Familie"
  },
  {
    "question": "profession",
    "answer": "der Beruf"
  },
  {
    "question": "teacher (female)",
    "answer": "die Lehrerin"
  },
  {
    "question": "man / husband",
    "answer": "der Mann"
  },
  {
    "question": "daughter",
    "answer": "die Tochter"
  },
  {
    "question": "son",
    "answer": "der Sohn"
  },
  {
    "question": "parents",
    "answer": "die Eltern"
  },
  {
    "question": "name",
    "answer": "der Name"
  },
  {
    "question": "cook / chef",
    "answer": "der Koch"
  },
  {
    "question": "wife / woman",
    "answer": "die Frau"
  },
  {
    "question": "doctor (male)",
    "answer": "der Arzt"
  },
  {
    "question": "doctor (female)",
    "answer": "die Ärztin"
  },
  {
    "question": "student (male)",
    "answer": "der Student"
  },
  {
    "question": "student (female)",
    "answer": "die Studentin"
  },
  {
    "question": "brother",
    "answer": "der Bruder"
  },
  {
    "question": "salesperson",
    "answer": "der Verkäufer"
  },
  {
    "question": "grandparents",
    "answer": "die Großeltern"
  },
  {
    "question": "grandmother",
    "answer": "die Großmutter"
  },
  {
    "question": "sister",
    "answer": "die Schwester"
  },
  {
    "question": "dog",
    "answer": "der Hund"
  },
  {
    "question": "boyfriend / friend (male)",
    "answer": "der Freund"
  },
  {
    "question": "programmer (female)",
    "answer": "die Programmiererin"
  },
  {
    "question": "programmer (male)",
    "answer": "der Programmierer"
  },
  {
    "question": "aunt",
    "answer": "die Tante"
  },
  {
    "question": "uncle",
    "answer": "der Onkel"
  },
  {
    "question": "country",
    "answer": "das Land"
  },
  {
    "question": "city",
    "answer": "die Stadt"
  },
  {
    "question": "the father",
    "answer": "der Vater"
  },
  {
    "question": "the mother",
    "answer": "die Mutter"
  },
  {
    "question": "the parents",
    "answer": "die Eltern"
  },
  {
    "question": "the brother",
    "answer": "der Bruder"
  },
  {
    "question": "the sister",
    "answer": "die Schwester"
  },
  {
    "question": "the son",
    "answer": "der Sohn"
  },
  {
    "question": "the daughter",
    "answer": "die Tochter"
  },
  {
    "question": "the grandfather",
    "answer": "der Großvater"
  },
  {
    "question": "the grandmother",
    "answer": "die Großmutter"
  },
  {
    "question": "the grandparents",
    "answer": "die Großeltern"
  },
  {
    "question": "the uncle",
    "answer": "der Onkel"
  },
  {
    "question": "the aunt",
    "answer": "die Tante"
  },
  {
    "question": "the husband",
    "answer": "der Mann"
  },
  {
    "question": "the wife",
    "answer": "die Frau"
  },
  {
    "question": "the boyfriend",
    "answer": "der Freund"
  },
  {
    "question": "the girlfriend",
    "answer": "die Freundin"
  }
]

